moreshare.com 2009-06-28

# Data Privacy Policy

**About This Page**   
This is a privacy policy for softwarepricing.com (the "Site"), which is published by SoftwarePricingPartners, Inc. 

**Data We Collect**

**_Access Log Information_**  
We collect information on visitors to our site for the following purposes:

* Completion and support of the current activity.   

* Web site and system administration.   

* Research and development.   

* Anonymous user analysis.   

* Anonymous user profiling and decision-making. 

This access log has been marked as non-identifiable. This means that there is no reasonable way for the Site to identify the individual person from whom we collected this data. 

**_Cookies_**  
We collect HTTP cookies. Cookies are a technology that can be used to provide you with tailored information from the Site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

We use cookies for site administration and ...  

* Completion and support of the current activity.   

* Web site and system administration.   

* Research and development.   

* Anonymous user analysis.   

* Anonymous user profiling and decision-making. 

Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you. We also use cookies to control access to certain content on our site. 

**_Mail List Information_**  
We collect the information about people who wish to join our mail list so we can send them a periodic e-mail. We always give people a way to opt-in or opt-out of our mailings. 

When we ask for identifying information so you can access information on the site, you can elect not to join our maillist. If you say you do not want to join we respect that and will not send unwanted e-mail to you. Even if you choose not to join our maillist, we still let you view our materials but this policy may change in the future.

We do not and have not shared our mail list with any other party. However, we may call to the attentiuon of our e-mail list subscribers information that we feel will be pertinent and of interest to them. This information is carefully screened to ensure it would be useful however, since it comes from thrid-parties, we cannot guarantee accuracy or continued availability.

**_Links to third-party sites_**  
We may provide links to third-party Web sites as a service to our users. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of such third-party Web sites, which may differ from those of this Site. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies on these Web sites before providing any information to them. 

**_Accessing, Change, and/or Deleting Information_**  
You may access, correct, update, and/or delete any personally-identifiable information that you have submitted to the Site. You may also unsubscribe from mailing lists or any registrations on the Site. If you want to be removed from our company database, please let us know and we will do so promptly. Just send an e-mail to unsubscribe@softwarepricing.com.

If you wish to mail us such a request, send it to SoftwarePricingPartners, Inc., 35 Main Street, Wayland, MA 01778..

_**Consent**_  
By using the Site, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the Site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 1 September 2004.
